You see,
the regime is collapsing.
The day that Mr. Putin defeated Mr. Rouhani and
Erdogan, remember when I said
the fortress was gone, meaning I can say that it was in a state of
waiting to see where the game would end,
and then the Americans threw the ball in the so-called crisis or
national movement in Venezuela.
Mr. Putin panicked, made a mistake from a
tactical point of view, and Venezuela lost its
focus on Iran. Why don't you remember that
Mr. Putin is still the godfather of this regime
in the game of the global mafia? You can't
cut it yourself, and his so-called minions or workers can
take the leader of that godfather and
throw him on the street. It has to be with his permission. Okay. Okay.
When the Americans put the arrival of the IRGC in the
sanctions and put the leader in the sanctions, everyone
realized
that there was a possibility that a compromise had been made between Mr. Trump and
Mr. Putin.
You got it.
Yes,
everyone is now in this panic and fear that
Putin will really abandon them.   The
first person to leave is the beginning.   Yes
.
Then the IRGC leaders, and then, according to you, the
Larijanis
.  But what you see now inside
Tehran, let me put it this way, you see in the vicinity of
Tehran, is the horror of collapse,
and everyone tries to get caught before they get caught, like the
Shah's generals or the Shah's high-ranking officials, in
that impasse of
closing the airport by Mr. Bakhtiar and then the arrival of the
Imam, according to their own words
.  They try to escape before an
incident occurs in which they
become victims.   There is no
place.
Look, that's why, look,
how can I say that?  I think they think
foreigners are troublemakers.  Okay?  When Mrs.
Mehrangiz works with 5 people, whenever I see their names, I get
suspicious. First, Akbar Ganjieh,
then Mehranangizh Kar, then that Masoumeh
Qomieh. They are always doing their job. Ali
Afsharieh, you know what I want. Mohsen Sazger.
You can't believe 100 percent. They are
doing something.
They have a mission to do something. When Mrs.
Mehrangiz comes, she posts a video,
signs it first, and then she comes to say, "Do
n't let it collapse. Don't let us
reach the conclusion that we have to massacre. No one wants to
massacre. I have never heard
anyone give a ruling. Even the simplest Iranians
who write on Facebook that after the
collapse of the Islamic Republic's Jim regime, for example, we
will hold a Nuremberg trial and hang everyone
or take them to Guillaume. No
one has said anything like that. So they themselves know that something is
happening, and they are afraid that something will happen to them after the
collapse.
The fact is that everyone will
die. You will see that even those who
are in the fake opposition
will disappear. They will gradually become silent and
go back to their posts. Don't worry at all
because the key has been set to
overthrow the regime.
Who has Mr. Donald Zabel entrusted the task to? Mr.
Pompeo.
Mr. Pompeo is lining them up one by one.
You see, bringing Israel
into the Persian Gulf is the
biggest tactical and strategic psychological blow
that the regime will suffer.
How is it that the Islamic Republic regime, which until yesterday
claimed that it had defeated the Shah from Karbala to Jerusalem and was
entering Jerusalem and conquering it, suddenly found itself
stranded not only in Karbala but also
because of the incidents that have occurred, and every
day Mr. Netanyahu bombs their
warehouses and so-called
facilities?
Look at them. They don't know what to
do now.  I told you, that's why the admiral
comes and says, "We went and signed a secret treaty with Putin,
and soon the
Russian fleet will come to the Persian Gulf."  No, Mr. Putin, my dear Alireza,
took the blame.
Okay,
this is the biggest booty,
how can I say it was political? Why did
Mr. Rejinsky, the greatest theorist of the Democrats
and the system,
write a book one day? The last book is almost the
last one and he said that our biggest goal is to
create a Southern Balkans in the south of Russia, that is, Russia, Mr. Putin, that means to divide that whole
region. I mentioned Azerbaijan,
Georgia, I don't know, Turkmenistan, Kazakhstan,
Kazakhstan, and even Afghanistan. We will take this from
Putin and then divide Russia.
Yes,
Mr. Putin took
our business and gave it to this oligarch. He
worked for Azerbaijan, Turkmenistan. Okay, there was no
greater victory for him than this.
That means he felt relieved that they would
not stand against him. That's right, they are now
setting up a joint-stock company.
Today was yesterday. I saw that Ms. Shirin Hunter had
written an article warning him. This lady
always warns about Iran's issues.
Very nice lady, she is also aware.
Where is she? She is
in Washington. Her husband, Robert Hunter,
was Brzezinski's deputy and later became the so-called
US representative to NATO.
She is a tough guy.  Hunter wrote on Lobolog, the same site where all the
Democrats and liberals write about Mr. Trump, "Be
careful, Putin took this Caspian Sea.
Now he has a plan to come and take Bushehr and the Chaba. Okay,
this is a warning. That's why I told my
dear friend,
Mr. Alireza Amirghasemi, last week when we were sitting together, we said to him, "We played badly.
We should have played the Caspian card
and the anti-Putin anti-Russia wave and won.
Now I don't know. Let's
go to such and such a place to protest. This is not it. You have to
create a wave
like a tsunami. Okay, Putin and his
so-called partners in the military really feel that they
cannot do such a thing. Otherwise, you
will lose badly. Okay,
but you say that Putin has
taken this bribe. If anything happens to the system,
it can come back again. And that's why
Putin will not allow
anyone to come and tear this system apart.
Okay,
this is a chess game, so to
speak.  It's unbelievable
how you can see that
Donald played a chess game, four-dimensional, and
put the Chinese in the Akmas. Okay,
now he supports Hong Kong and the youth of Hong Kong, who
warned me today that they should be
careful, you can't go on a campaign. This is
for these young people. Okay. The second point is that Venezuela came and went.
Mr. Putin didn't go to Venezuela. That means
you, as a chess player, shouldn't change your pieces.
Okay?
Okay, he went and settled in Venezuela, so
to speak, with an advisor, meaning another front.  Now
they came, opened a third front, came and
surrounded Iran,
took control of the Persian Gulf, and as soon as
Putin came, made a so-called
exceptional move or Iranian gambit and
saved the regime, they started to disrupt Moscow.
Yes, that
means you have to see and evaluate all the games one by one
.  Why?  For Putin,
demonstrations in Moscow are a
credit.
He is the godfather of that Kremlin.
Now, those Silevskys are that group, not the
oligarchs.  Oligarchs have financial stakes
.  The power that is the Kremlin's shadow government
asks this question.  How long can we
stand behind Putin?  This is it.  What I'm saying is that they know
how to train it.
Okay, okay, let's be
brief because we have time. Let me ask this, then we'll go back and do it
again.
One of the advantages that the Islamic Republic has for itself
is that it always talks about its power
.
How strong we are, how much power we
have.  They even showed pictures of the British
fleeing.  We followed them, the
English boat was escaping.  All these issues will be
rewritten later, saying
that we are the fourteenth largest army in Iran
and the tenth largest in Israel.  Who are these for
and who are these shows for?  Is it for the
people inside the country or is it because the people are
outside the country or because of what these governments say?   The
governments themselves know where they stand
.
Incidentally, you have made a nice point.  Look,
my dear,
these are the most powerful forces in the Middle East.
Every day Israel comes and bombs Syria
, bombs Iraq, they do
n't make a sound.
Why don't they talk?  Why?  When
those so-called slums were
bombed in Iraq, where they even say that some of the so-called
shrapnel reached the American embassy, ​​why didn't they
say a word?  So, this Qassem Rambouillet who
they say has gone underground and is
actually implementing hidden plans and strategies,
where is he?  Well,
if
those who claimed to be the
opposition abroad had played Putin's card today,
this regime would have
lost 50% of its credibility and position at home.
We are dealing with the inside. They see everything
as a concert. Remember the first time I
spoke to you, I said that those who came to
Million Square, don't you want to hold a concert? They
advertise every day. They
advertise concerts. You, God, are doing this.
Well,
political struggle is not like you come and
ask. In fact, you announce it in the form of a poster.
We are going. There is no such thing. In the
same square, the square or the Ukrainian square,
an Afghan kid with an internet connection
drew young people to the square.
First 100 people came, then 100 people,
then suddenly 20,300,000 people gathered in that square. Did
n't you see the Egyptian revolution?
That young friend of mine came with Google and brought the young people
first. What did they do on the streets of Hong Kong? They
told each other in Pokemon that, for example, we had an appointment to
occupy the airport.
So the
struggle has a strategy, a plan, and a
program.  You can't just pretend that you're starting a
movement or revolution
.  There is no such thing, my dear.
But it can be good advertising for people
inside the country.  1. Look at this regime now.
I always said it. I'll say it again. I said 10 years
ago that we would reach an Iranian Renaissance. At the same time,
in 15 years, I was saying that
Iranian Cinderellas are the Achilles' heel of this regime.
Okay, now they've come to hijack an artist and play a
game. Okay, what did I say next? I said that a
new generation has arrived and this regime has fallen
asleep from sleepless terror.
Alireza, this stylish generation of Pasargadae has
truly become the biggest so-called
scapegoat of this regime.  They don't know what to
do at all.  That's why you're in a sticky situation
on both sides until the
next move.
This widow ratio is part of the system itself.
That is, they
learned so many things that this system itself
brought them to, and now they can't answer them. Well done, you
see. The Mujahideen, the Tudeh, or those
guerrillas of the people, were revolutionary twins. Everyone did it their
own way. Okay, they didn't all take orders from Mr. Khomeini. The Tudeh
had a form. The Mujahideen of Religion
were waiting to overthrow the regime and take over.
But now, well done, you've said the most correct thing so far.
Well done,
these kids are coming up in this regime.
Today or yesterday, someone wrote on my Facebook, "
Uncle Mano, my Basij friends are also joining the
stylish generation of Pasargadi,
Basij friends. Why are these kids from the same neighborhood
playing Golchik together in the same neighborhood?
A new image is being seen. It's
actually a run-in between the Emirates and Iran.
Okay, what's
this story? On the one hand, we're seeing
Sheikh Mohammed
kissing Bin Salman's face, and these good relations between
Saudi Arabia and the Emirates are from one place, but on the
other hand, because we're careful.  Let them be themselves and be
careful of the Gulf so that nothing happens to them.
They are playing catch-up with Iran and, as the saying goes,
wink.  Look, if you
remember, it was a month ago, about a month
ago, when the leader of Qatar came.
Yes, that's right.
Qatar is a more suitable pawn for a strategic game than the Emirates from a strategic point of view,
from a financial perspective, and from a perspective of the presence of
American military bases in that country.
Secondly, they sent the Emirates to
enter into negotiations with the Islamic Republic. No, from a
perspective of nothing at all. There are three issues: three islands and
Pars, the South Pars oil gas region. So the
Sheikh himself felt that it was possible that with the
agreements that are being made,
the world, as I have mentioned many times, is divided between the
two energy poles of the world,
Putinista and Trumpista. Okay, the
Sheikh of the Emirates has this illusion that
they are likely to sacrifice Rome. Why is it
because the world is now about the
world's gas pipelines? If you are in this
area of ​​pipelines, you are the subject of the so-
called political respect game.
If you pay attention,
one of the causes of the Syrian war was this gas pipeline
that was supposed to go from Iran to Syria
to Europe. Oh, okay,
yes,
for the Western world.  It was dangerous, and Israel is
now exporting gas itself, and do
n't forget Putin's Putin. Putin has been in
conflict with the West for years over Nord Stream and South Stream. Why does
he want the entire European gas market to
be at his disposal? So the Sheikh of the Emirates has
preferred to enter into negotiations over the three islands for now
to see how they decide on the issue of his region or the
South Pars field.
Because it is possible. You see, I am
mentioning here that it is not the same as the easy
Caspian and the removal of Iran's quota
there.
So now both
sides are trying to negotiate with each other so that everyone
has their share. And don't be in doubt.
The issue is the South Pars gas field. Okay, let's
go. The Emirates is always
sensitive to people, big and small. So, you
see, dear Ali Rezaei.
Now, if the Emirates insists on the three
islands,
yes,
with the British fleet, which was once the master of these, you ca
n't say no. He turned all of this
into a sheikhdom,
right?
Okay, with the British elites, the American elites, isn't it
possible that another Falklands war could break out
in that region?
So for now, the UAE, considering that it
has a strong military backing and a powerful genius, has
entered into negotiations. If it wanted to negotiate with the Islamic Republic a few months ago, the
Islamic Republic would not have accepted them at all.
Now, it has to actually beg to
come to the negotiating table. Don't forget this. Let's go back to
Iran today and Mike Pompeo is saying
different things about Iran again. Then, on the
other hand,
his representative, now his right hand or his left hand or one of his
children, Brian Hook, comes and tells the people of Iran, "Come on,
start this hashtag, and these
different hashtags that we want freedom,
what could be the reason for this?"
Look,
they are making the
game legal, right? I
mean, is this the problem? Look,
you see,
they are doing it as Yi Kosher said.
Look, they don't want to be labeled as warmongers in the world.
Okay, okay,
so they are making this regime look bad every day,
and they believe
100%, but they believe to a high degree
that people will come and people
will stand up to this regime. I told you, they
will bring people to the streets. They
just need to feel that
they have a relative alternative inside the country. Do
n't forget this. They always pay
attention to Gorbachev's time. It took 3 years for
Gorbachev to overthrow Mr. Yeltsin.
Then the game was over. Russia was divided.
All property was looted. All the
nuclear keys to Rome were taken from them. Rest
assured, Mike Pompeo is
not a good chess player.  Okay,
but he's a man who
knows the games of psychological warfare very well, and
look, from the day they came, they
fired Zarif with psychological warfare. Why?
My dear Alireza Zarif was not only the face,
image, or voice of that system, he was one of its
men.
Okay?  That is, someone who Trump and his supporters can't stand at all
.  Therefore, preferring such a player
who can one day launch a
colorful or velvet movement along with the Jerash team as they wish
.  These actually take out the coefficient
.  Now, no matter how much they want to be arrogant,
no matter how much they say, we are also fragile, yes, everyone is
fragile because they are falling apart.  But
that was the main point of getting them out
.  His relationship with George, who himself revealed himself, was
just a year and a half or two years ago. He came and said, "
I controlled the clubs of the
so-called rebel activists in Iran
."  So you should have a relationship
like Mr. Khatami
right.  Okay, okay,
so this is where they have
effectively eliminated the regime by removing its main motivator.
Now what does the regime want to do without
Zarif, and Rouhani himself is not a number now? Let me
tell you, what they
say is "We are Zarif" or is it the same
Spartacus game where I am Spartacus? This
story and these issues are about the leadership. Does the
leadership also believe in this?  No, the leadership is so
happy that they don't know what to do that Zarif and
others were removed. They were a problem for him.
Look at Zarif, Rouhani, and the Ministry of
Foreign Affairs team, the provincial department, and the coefficient. Look at him. He was
very rude. He
told them to go talk. He didn't expect
Trump to come and so-called tear
up the JCPOA.  No, no, he wouldn't have imagined such a thing at all
.  He was looking to create a
game of chess and actually make these things
happen,
and it happened.  This is why he says every day that he
sent them to negotiate and
find out how deceitful America is.   Okay
.  So,
if you look closely,
they are blaming Rafsanjani
because they believe that Rafsanjani is an American pawn. Do
n't hesitate at all. Why did a woman
named Shahrzad bring this statement? Mr.
Rafsanjani gave
documents and, so to speak, all of our information to the
Americans.  The same one who worked for Zarqami
.
Okay?   Yes
How could you allow yourself to say that
Rafsanjani was an American?  This
cannot be denied.  He took a very revolutionary stance.   He
played a lot.
When Mr. Khoeniha, the
so-called godfather of the occupiers and hostage-takers, returned, the
first thing he did was insult Rafsanjani
and then said, "If he didn't defend us, we should
defend them." It showed that the Islamic left had
returned, the
coupists had returned, and they were standing against the
American current group. Don't forget
that.  Now, in fact, the
Russophile faction or the Islamic left is standing against a group
that wants to negotiate with America.   Do
n't forget this.  Now you will ask,
why did the Americans expel Zarif?  Because
if you remember, Zarif kept saying after the JCPOA that
we shouldn't negotiate.   He said
we had our negotiations.   Well done
.  Throw it out.  Saying you don't want to
negotiate.  Welcome.  But America did
n't want to talk to Zarif himself either.
Look, on the first day I said, "Anyone who negotiated with Obama
is forbidden fruit for them."
Okay,
okay.
Now, will they negotiate with Rouhani? I don't think they
will negotiate with Mr. Rouhani. With this
puppet show that they're starting, maybe
they're planning to kick Mr. Rouhani out and appoint someone to
come and negotiate.  Do
n't forget this,
because the Leader of the Islamic Republic himself is also
not willing to negotiate with this, because contrary to
everything he says, exactly, exactly.
But we must also
pay attention to this. How long can he say no
war, no negotiations?
Well, the
regime has collapsed.   Do
n't you think the regime itself likes war
?
Yes, but they are very vigilant in trying not to
enter the war, and if they do enter the
war, I think they will defeat the proxy forces of the
Islamic Republic.  That is, all the branches of the
Quds Force. Donald Trump's only trump card
is that the Islamic Republic regime's case is closed. The
greatest victory is like the collapse of the Soviet Union. Do
n't forget this.
Why should he go to war that will last for years and then remain in the
Middle East mess? He wants to get out of the Middle East.
You, so to speak, close the Islamic Republic booth just like the
communism booth was closed. They will all
collapse. They will collapse. It's very
simple.
And the Islamic Republic
can be
believed that it will be
destroyed or the system
will change just as easily.
Reza, we met for the first time last year.
Yes, did
you think that the Islamic Republic regime would
reach this point?
No,
such sanctions really put a noose around their necks
and put pressure on them?  No, look,
political games are
security games.
If you don't understand security games, you will never be able to
solve them or, so to speak,
analyze them.  Look, if you
didn't know the Reynard Kipling network, you would
never be able to comment on the British Empire and its
decline.  Why?  He was the one who sent Lawrence
and Mrs. Lepan and Mrs. Gretou Double and I don't know,
all of them, to the Middle East and it
became an empire.
Now, have you ever asked yourself why the
Soviet Union suddenly fell?
Why did King Philby go to the Soviet Union as
a trilateral spy? Then we saw that
in the Soviet Union, it was like, "Okay, the same things are
happening in Iran."
When Mr. Abbasi
repeats our words and accuses the intelligence service of "
you came and started the news," he
means all those so-called
street demonstrations or whatever happened in Tehran, in which
you played a role,
meaning you are part of the subversives.
I always said that you
cannot bring down a system without the help of the intelligence service,
but only on the condition that you
play so carefully that they don't
swallow you up.
That was the difference between the Americans and the Soviets
.  Don't be fooled by people who come and make up stories
.
Every time those who came as nationals or as infiltrators
heard what they said, even four pages of people were
sent back. And now if you look at
Mike Pompeo as an
intelligence figure,
look at how he deals with the foreign community. Okay,
because he knows, because he has evaluated and weighed, he knows
which pieces he should accept and which
pieces he should not accept. Rest assured, one
day, maybe
we will all be surprised. The
last word, or according to your opinion, regarding the
next events that are going to happen,
I am saying that you should not get caught up in the Hosseini passion. This is a
term that
Reza Nazanin repeats left and right.
Hosseini passion. And she is exactly right.
We always get caught up in this passion. We enter the game.
Some of our media friends
actually pull the fuses and
excite them. Then they believe that all these
pieces, who are actually national fighters,
should not be insulted. They are
fighting. There is no such thing. Most of
these pieces are their own creations.  Remember
why the dear Ali Reza Reza of the regime, after he
took over and started executing the Mujahideen and their rivals,
then started making excuses?  Yes, for
a long time now, the regime has not been making you repent, but rather has been making you
polite.  It's polite to do what the
system wants you to do and do it on time
.  That's why you see so many articles today, the most
obvious example of which for me is the arrest of Mr. Zeidabadieh and Mr.
Tajzadeh. I have great respect for Abadi,
but look now that they write, the
last line is always different. It's not what
you would expect. Even Hajjarian has become polite. Do
n't think that he has made
everyone polite.  That's why, instead of getting carried away by
Hosseini's enthusiasm, let's first
read the games, not wait for them to happen and
then come and sell the favor that we are analyzing
.  Thank you very much
for staying with us until the end of the video.
Please write your comments below this video
for us and other friends, and help spread awareness by liking,
subscribing, and sharing the video
.